

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

R programming Statistics Python SQL Data visualization Machine learning

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learning
Motivated

CONTACT

- +55 19 998095841
- gustavomig@gmail.com

LINKS

- https://gustavomigliorini.netlify.app/
- in linkedin.com/in/gustavo-h-migliorini-87a00b35
- https://github.com/ghmigliorini
- researchgate.net/profile/Gustavo-H-Migliorini

GUSTAVO H. MIGLIORINI

DATA SCIENTIST

ABOUT

Data scientist with PhD and broad experience with scientific research, data analysis and statistical analyses using programming languages such as R, Python and SQL. Ability to solve problems independently and fast learning, critical thinker and proactive.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DATA ANALYST

ALS Life Sciences | Feb 2022 - Dec 2022

- Analyses of clinical research data
- Validation of statistical results
- Review of statistical reports

RESEARCH DATA ANALYST

Federal University of Pernambuco | May 2021 - Dec 2021

- Analyses of research data
- Teaching of R programming and statistical analyses
- Design of research experiments
- Scientific writing and publication

EDUCATION

DATA SCIENCE SPECIALIST

Federal University of Technology - Paraná | Mar 2021 - Nov 2022

- Programming languages (R, Python)
- Databases (SQL)
- Big Data
- Machine Learning
- Deep Learning

Final project: Identification of birds from Brazil through deep learning for image classification

PHD - ENVIRONMENTAL SCIENCES

State University of São Paulo | March 2014 - November 2018

- Experiment design;
- Data collection;
- Data and statistical analyses;
- Scientific writing and publication;

CERTIFICATES

STATISTICAL ANALYSES WITH R

UNIVARIATE STATISTICS WITH R